dxomark.com 2009-06-19

# Privacy Policy

**5\. Privacy Policy**

DxO Labs is committed to respecting your privacy and to complying with applicable data protection and privacy laws. This Site has been registered with the Commission Nationale de l’Informatique et des Libertés (French National Data Processing and Liberties Commission). DxO Labs reserves the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy provisions at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation.

**5.1. Collection and use of personal information**

DxO Labs acknowledges that it could collect and use your personal information only with your consent and in accordance with the law of January 6, 1978 relating to computing, files and liberties and with Article 43 of the modified law of September 30, 1986. Typically when you benefit from an extended use, answer users enquiries, register for information or other services, or when you respond to DxO Labs communications (such as questionnaires or surveys) DxO Labs may collect such personal information. If you choose to provide DxO Labs with personal information, it will be used in support of the intended purposes stated at the time at which it was collected, and subject to any preferences indicated to you. You acknowledge that by providing data to DxO Labs, you consent to the processing of your data in accordance with this section.

**5.2. Access to your personal Information**

Under the provisions of the aforementioned law of January 6, 1978, you are informed of your right of access to and modification of information provided about yourselves. To exercise these rights, please write to: DxO Labs Marketing Department, 3 rue Nationale, 92100 Boulogne Billancourt – France

**5.3. Information Security**

Please be aware that communications over the Internet, such as emails/web mails, are not secure unless they have been encrypted. DxO Labs cannot accept responsibility for any unauthorized access or loss of personal information that is beyond its control. ****

**5.4. Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small file which is placed on the user's hard drive during Site visit. This file allows the user to move quickly and easily around our Site. It is also used to identify returning users and, should the case arise, to identify subscribers and registrants (a registrant or a subscriber will have the cookie linked to its e-mail address as a way of identifying him). This means that if you are a registrant or subscriber, you will not have to login each time you visit. DxO Labs may also use a cookie to track user's sessions. You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time. Bear in mind, though, that if you delete these cookies, any settings such as your stored username and password will have to be reset when you log in again. You will be able to use the Site even if you set your browser not to accept any cookies. However, certain features and content may not be available to you and you will have to log in every time you visit.

**5.5. Links to other sites**

The Site may offer links to sites managed by other companies. These sites may also collect personal and non personal data. Consultation of these sites and the collection and use of personal data on these sites is subject to the terms of use and personal data protection policies of those sites. DxO Labs cannot be held liable for their contents or for the use of the data you supply to those sites.
